<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Above on MiniCurtains</title><link>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/</link><description>Recent content in Above on MiniCurtains</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://minicurtains.github.io/above/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 1</title><link>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter1/</guid><description>They appeared at midnight. Three men in white suits with dark sunglasses which could hide a soul. Just pop! Out of thin air. The dim street lamp glowed as the men walked, more like glided up to the doorstep of number 12 Endworth Way. The middle one knocked. Silence. Then suddenly a trap door flung open and the three men fell, not even flinching. The people who lived in the surrounding houses were still.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2</title><link>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter2/</guid><description>The world swam in front of his eyes and his knees buckled. The car door flung open and out jumped a woman with bright red hair and deep green eyes. In the car still sat what Oliver assumed was her husband. &amp;ldquo;Oh my god. What have I done?! Help!&amp;rdquo; she screamed, &amp;ldquo;Help!&amp;rdquo;. Oliver looked down and saw his limp body lying on the wet road. The front door of Oliver&amp;rsquo;s house opened and his mother and father came into the street.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3</title><link>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minicurtains.github.io/above/chapter3/</guid><description>When Oliver woke up he was in the boot of a car. He could tell this from the smell of petrol, the rough movement of the car on the road and the shape of the space he was trapped in. A sliver of light crept onto his face and the blue glinting eyes of the man from before are all Oliver could see. &amp;ldquo;Ready?&amp;rdquo; the man asked in a smooth voice.</description></item></channel></rss>